freemulticoins.com 2015-11-01

# Privacy policy | FreeMultiCoins - free bitcoins / litecoins / dogecoins in one place!

This policy regulates the procedure and use cases by FreeMultiCoins personal information on websites FreeMultiCoins in general and how you can control the use of these data. The term "computer" in this document are indicated by computers, smartphones and other devices that allow users to access the Internet. The Policy on a cookie relates to any of our websites, meaning any website or mobile application, which is administered by FreeMultiCoins, its subsidiaries or affiliates, or on behalf of FreeMultiCoins, its subsidiaries or affiliates irrespective of the manner in which you obtained access to the network.

This policy is part of the conditions of use of the website posted the link http://freemulticoins.com/privacy

Items considered:

**1\. Collect information.  
2\. Using the information collected.  
3\. Block and delete personal information.  
4\. Protection of information.  
5\. Other.**

## **1\. Information Collection**

We collects 2 types of data - the data that we get from users, and data collection which is carried out automatically.

1.1 The information provided by users - information on the e-mail address, name, shipping address, phone number and index, obtained by pressing a user on the "Register".  
1.2 The information obtained in automatic mode - data web visitors that are automatically collected resource freemulticoins.com. Google Analytics (hereinafter - "GA") - free tools from Google, which allow website owners to study the behavior of visitors to their websites. For more information, see GA. on the official web page of the service for posylannyamhttp: //www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/.

Yandex.Metrika - a free tool that helps boost performance advertising website. Metric allows monitoring of key performance indicators website analyze user behavior and evaluate the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. For more information, see service. Web site https://metrika.yandex.com/.

When you visit any of your website your browser transmits information about you tools GA. In GA account, we get the following:

demographic information (such as information on age, gender, language, country, operating system, browser);  
data on interests (sports, games and so on. f.);  
data on the behavior of (new or repeat customer, how much time a customer spends on a website, number of pages);  
data on attracting customers (where learned about the site - a direct reference, referral, organic search, and so on. d.).  
Tools GA cookie files are used to store information about you.

What is a cookie?

File cookie - are small pieces of data that contain the unique identifier that is sent to the server the website to your computer's browser and stored on your hard drive. Every web site or a third-party service provider that uses the website can send your own files cookie to your browser if your browser allows to do so; but the protection of personal data, Web browser allows Web site or a third-party service provider to access only those files cookie, which sent earlier. A cookie containing anonymous information - a unique identifier, called a website and some digital and statistics. This allows the website to remember your settings or store information on the goods added to the basket. A cookie can be assembly work of stored on your session time use of a service, or immediately deleted once you close brazuer. Also cookie files can be permanent and stored in memory for a long time browsing.

More information about cookie files see. the web page https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/27448?hl=en.

What is a browser?

Browser - is an application that allows you to view Web sites on the Internet. Among the most popular browsers - Chrome, Internet Explorer, Firefox and Safari. Most browsers are safe and make it possible to quickly and easily remove information such as cookie.

You can choose how the cookie files used by your device by changing your browser settings. Popular browsers allow cookie handle files as follows: a) take all files cookie; b) to report files cookie; c) not to accept files cookie; if you choose not to accept a cookie, the website might stop work effectively and provide service in full. Each browser is different, so we recommend that you contact the Help program to learn the details of the settings and files cookie.

Cookie and personal data

Actually cookie files can not tell us your e-mail address or other personal information for as long as you do not provide it, for example, registering at one at our websites. Once you give your consent to provide your personal information, this information will be immediately added to the data files cookie. Files cookie - it's something like an ID card. They are unique to your computer and can only be read by the server to which it was supplied.

## **2\. Use of collected information**

2.1 Email address - the only way to contact you. We use your email address:

send special offers on the website freemulticoins.com;  
notification of new devices available on the website freemulticoins.com;  
answers to questions sent via contact form or e-mail info@freemulticoins.com.  
2.2. Data from GA and services Yandex.Metrika allow us to analyze website audiences freemulticoins.com. We use the cookie to improve the functionality of websites, based on the information on their use, and to improve the content of our web sites and proposals submitted to them. We can also use a cookie to offer you products and services.

Generally, we use a cookie, that:

ensure proper security as well as check and remember your personal information, so you do not need to enter them each time you just go to a new page;  
Remember your decision to preserve user name and password that you do not had to enter them each time you visit a website;  
Remember that content is the most important for you, allowing you to change web pages, complementing their information that may interest you;  
ensure that the purchase of a particular type of product or service through our Web sites is fast and safe;  
collect and store anonymous information which will allow us to better understand how visitors use our website and how we can improve the structure of our website.  
On our Web sites are used as sessional and permanent files cookie.

We tell you how you can control the type of files each cookie.

File Types cookie, which can be used during a session on our website:

A cookie to personalize. These files cookie used to learn which users returned to the site for the first time, and use the information entered them earlier (which is why when you are browsing the website pages that are accessed earlier, you need not again enter the information provided ). These files are used to recommend content which, in our opinion, can you please. You can disable your cookie to personalize came out of the account in Facebook. In order to permanently disable a cookie, you will need to uninstall Mirror Settings page of your account to Facebook.  
A cookie for site management. These cookie files are used to store data or session ID in the website. For example, when our sites are more than one server, we use cookie files in order to ensure that the information you send one particular server (otherwise you unexpectedly logged in or out of it). We can use similar files cookie, when you participate in a vote that you vote once and can use the commenting even when not logged in (in order to hide comments that you find offensive, as well as to Comments not vote for more than once). These cookie files can be disabled separately, but you can reset your browser to prohibit all files cookie, if you do not want to use them.  
A cookie foreign services and service analytics. Buttons social networks, video and other services of our website are property of other companies. These companies may also use a cookie on your computer when you use them in our websites or they were previously registered.  
Here are the web pages where you can learn more about the services we use and their policies for files cookie:

Politics processing of personal data Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other

AddThis (service that allows management of social buttons on our web site): http: //www.addthis.com/privacy#.T6j--usS0bw

Privacy Policy Twitter: https://twitter.com/privacy

Terms of use Storify (a service that is sometimes used to post tweets on our website): http://storify.com/tos

Politics cookie file of the video player YouTube: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/faq/#toc-cookies(стандартні rules Google).

2.3. We use remarketing tools GA. They allow us to show ads to users who previously visited our website on other websites. Service AdWords helps us to use this feature. For example, if you add some products to the basket and decided not to buy them at this time. In this case, we can show promotional offers for these products. For more information about using these tools, see. storintsihttp on the web: //www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/.

Analytics

GA Service provides us with anonymous information about statistics. Service operates IP-addresses and information on a cookie, used on our websites, so we know how many people visit our site, how many among them are browsing certain web pages that browsers they use (which allows us to improve the compatibility of our services to more people) and, in some cases, or live where countries, cities and regions. Sometimes IP-addresses are processed outside the European Economic Area and, in this case, we ensure that their processing takes place in accordance with the Law on the protection of information.

## **3\. Block and delete personal information**

Many browsers allow you to refuse the use of files cookie. The following links will help you learn more about how you can manage cookie in your browser. Note, however, off a cookie is not limited to this, but other websites.

• Internet Explorer http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835 (This web page provides information about the various versions of IE. For information on the mobile version, see. On the website:  
www.microsoft.com/windowsphone/en-us/howto/wp7/web/changing-privacy-and-other-browser-settings.aspx)

• Chrome: http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=95647

• Safari: http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html (http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677для or mobile versions of the browser)

• Firefox: http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies

• Opera: http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/

Cookie blocking can adversely affect the operation of many websites.

You also have the option to delete a cookie, stored on your computer. Simply follow the instructions of the browser. But again, delete a cookie may make a negative impact on the work of many websites.

For more information about how to disable cookie-service, see GA. on the Web page:

Google Analytics: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout

For more information about deleting a cookie see. on the Web page: https: //support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050? hl = en

## **4\. Data Protection**

We do not sell, rent and provide not share information about our users to third parties. Personal information can be given exclusively to law enforcement or government agencies as required by law.

## **5\. Other**

Utilization websites FreeMultiCoins requires you to agree to the terms policy on DoubleClick cookie. If you disagree with its provisions do not visit websites and http://freemulticoins.com.

Action on a cookie policy applies to all services provided on web sites FreeMultiCoins.

We reserve the right from time to time without notice to amend the policy on DoubleClick cookie. For this reason we ask that you occasionally check this policy is to always be aware of changes and updates.

To ask your question about policy on file cookie, you can write to the email address: info@freemulticoins.com. Be sure to indicate which of the sites concerns your question.
